Today, myself, Josh, and JJ are going to
be brutally ranking YouTuber products,
putting them in a tier from S to C. Or
will they get an F, which means fail?
First one. Oh, the Mr. Beast briefcase.
>> The biggest YouTuber of all.
>> Is there money in it?
>> What's in a briefcase?
>> Let's find out. So, we have tears. S A B
C. Fail. Fail.
>> So, if it's absolutely stinky,
it's a fail. Can I get this part? Oh,
it's Is it a toy?
>> So, you get yourself a collector item.
>> I think it's the wrong way.
>> Oh. Oh, it's all falling apart. That's
your That's your fault, not his fault,
though.
>> That's Mr. Beast's fault.
>> No, it's your fault.
>> Why? Why not make it 50/50? So, I can do
it either way.
>> Facts. Facts. Facts. Smart.
>> Oh.
>> Oh. Okay.
>> All right. Some free chocolate.
>> Free bars.
>> It's just to clear up. It's not free. We
bought the
>> No, you bought You know, but you bought
a briefcase and got chocolate for free.
>> Okay. That's what we're doing.
>> That's one each. Yeah. There you go. One
for you, one for you, one for me. Mr.
Beast lab toy. Here we go. Pretty cool.
What else do we get?
>> You get um a postcard with a QR to
secret neverbefore seen video.
>> This one. Okay.
>> Is there a QR code on it?
>> There is.
>> Ah. So you can you can watch an
exclusive video just from the briefcase
watchers.
>> Okay.
>> Can I You want to watch it?
>> Let me see what it says.
>> Play that.
>> And then what's this?
>> That's cool.
>> This is like a one of one
>> collector item from Mr. Beast video set.
>> Wo. So
>> you just GOT ONE OF ONE MR. BEAST.
>> What is it? Is it what it is?
>> Limited edition authentic piece of the
tracksuits used in Mr. Beast ages. One
to 100. That's a sick video.
>> Jenny, you've cooked. You've actually
like that for the sports card.
>> Low key. No, I want to buy more. You get
other ones.
>> No, Josh. There's one.
>> No, but you can get you get other like
things.
>> Yeah, 100%. The question is, how much
was this?
>> Wait one sec. I've got the video.
>> Oh, bloody hell. It's 8 minutes.
>> I have built the most deadly obstacle
course in the world.
>> So, it's Mac doing an obstacle course.
>> Yeah, but he's already shown this.
>> Has he? It's exclusive. Oh, I think I
have seen this one. Yeah.
>> Yeah.
>> Maybe maybe he released it like
eventually.
>> How much would you pay for this?
>> Try me.
>> I'd say finger him.
>> It's a try me. It's a thing.
>> It has to be less than 100.
>> $80.
>> Three pieces of chocolate bar. I think
[music] that's like Oh, I haven't
actually tried the new one.
>> And also, but this this is big. I think
80 $90 be acceptable.
>> Well, American chocolate, by the way.
>> Joking.
>> Got me.
>> That's No, that's really good. By the
way, I hate American chocolate. That's
That's not American chocolate.
>> No,
>> I'd pay kind of chocolate.
>> 70 bucks. $90.
>> I'd say 40 makes sense. $40.
>> $50.
>> For that alone, I'd buy that on eBay for
$90. [laughter]
>> Oh god.
>> I'm going to give it eight.
>> Yeah, I'll give it eight.
>> Cuz it's not like it's not like a
mystery box. You You know what you're
getting.
>> Yeah.
>> You know you're getting these things.
It's for collectors. That is a mystery
box. [laughter]
>> But it's for collectors. You get exact
like you get this. That's a collector
item. Yeah. You get a toy. You get the
chocolate. Get chocolate.
[screaming]
[groaning]
>> You freed me. Thank you.
>> Let's get next item, shall we?
>> I reckon he has a [\h__\h]
>> What? You I
>> He doesn't.
>> A tier.
>> Yeah. A for now.
[laughter]
>> Look at this guy, man.
>> Oh, Leave him alone, MAN. [laughter]
LEAVE HIM ALONE. NO.
>> NEXT UP, Rod's coffee. [music] So,
that's a Willy and James Marriott,
right?
>> It is. I've actually never tried it.
>> I don't drink coffee.
>> Neither do I.
>> I I drink coffee, but not iced.
>> We have cold brew oat. We have waffle
oat, tiramisu,
>> and matcha. I don't want matcha.
>> I mean, I'll try I'll try them all.
>> Really?
>> Yeah.
>> I don't like any of them as in like the
flavors of them.
>> You haven't even tried it.
>> NO. I DON'T LIKE THE [laughter] MASCOT.
I've literally said multiple times that
I don't want to try this on camera
because there's no way I like it cuz I
don't like ice cream.
>> Zero dairy. There's 41 milligs of
caffeine.
>> Josh, this is for you. That one waffle
oat.
>> Zero dairy.
>> You're drinking waffle.
>> That's sick.
>> Yeah. Where's oat milk?
>> That's cold.
>> You sure that one's zero?
>> Yeah. Yeah, it's all zero dairy.
>> I'm wearing tiramisu.
>> I'm trying waffle.
>> Okay, I'll try and match up.
>> I'm sorry if I give this a bad rating
cuz I don't like
>> Do you want to go first?
>> You have friends who are investors, by
the way, so be careful. M.
>> That's the best thing I've ever had. Um,
it's all right. Like considering I don't
like iced coffee, it's it's okay.
>> Oh, what was that face Josh?
>> No, it's actually all right. To be fair,
too.
>> Yeah. Okay. How about the matcha one
>> with the vanilla?
>> I don't drink too coffee. That actually
is quite nice. That passively, I'd say.
I would drink that again.
>> As in you like it enough to drink it
again?
>> Yeah. I only drink coffee, so that's
actually pretty good.
>> I mean, I could drink this. Like, I
could drink the whole thing. I don't
like ice coffee, so I'm
>> I could drink this. [laughter]
>> NOT A REVIEW.
>> IT'S NOT A FAIR. I COULD I DRINK IT. I
could drink it.
>> I can't sit here and say it's amazing
cuz I don't like iced coffee.
>> Yeah.
>> You want to try a tiramisu?
>> I'm going to try it.
>> You had tiramisu before
>> as a dessert. Have that as a comparison.
Really?
>> Tiramisu.
>> Better or worse than the one you had?
>> I prefer the waffle. That actually
tastes a bit like waffle.
>> Waffle. Like what waffle?
>> I'm not a fan of the smell of this one.
>> That one's actually like
>> Well, that is better. That one is weird.
[laughter]
>> Oh, sorry. Oh, [\h__\h]
>> Try that one.
>> Not a fan of this one.
>> Try the waffle.
>> Cold brew oat latte. Yeah.
>> What's a cold brew? Is that like I don't
know.
>> That's just like coffee.
>> Oh god. [laughter]
>> Right. So, two out of four. You've gone
two. Do you want two of
>> Okay. Sorry. Got nuts in it. No.
>> I'd say I'd say this is definitely the
best by far. By far.
>> Is it match like mud? It's okay. I like
the waffle one the most.
>> Oh, that's cold.
>> I think they're like 1 180 each or
something like
>> 220.
>> Is that a lot?
[laughter]
>> Um, I'm going to give it a Me
personally, I don't like iced coffee, so
I'm going to give it a B.
>> Yeah, we're we're a bit like an awful
audience. Do you drink coffee ever?
Yeah.
>> So, you should be the person who rates
this because I he he could drink it.
>> Yeah, that's what I mean. Like, if it
was normal coffee, I'm going fail cuz I
can't drink coffee. I hate it.
>> I'm going to drink this and it's all
right. So, I'm going B.
>> I think B is acceptable. I
>> I was going to say B. It's not the best
coffee I've ever had in my life.
>> There's zero dairy, low sugar, zero
sugar.
>> Yeah. The fact that it's zero dairy is
huge. I'd say tastewise.
>> Like, it is. It is good.
>> These though?
>> No, those are the two I like.
>> Yeah. So, I mean I mean it's good for
everyone.
>> Product diversity is good, but the
chocolate though. [laughter]
>> Oh, I know what this one is. Oh, this is
Mark Robber's Crunch Labs. There's two
subscription services. One you can get
that's build it yourself. So, he shows
you a video and then you build it
yourself. The other one comes preong
with that.
>> But this is one. This is the same just
this was pre-built so we didn't have to
like
>> you know
>> what the hell is going on.
>> So, you got to throw the basketball I
guess.
>> Did you get it first time?
>> All right. Oh,
>> what's the point of the
>> I don't know the point of the water.
>> You need to um score as many as you can
before it goes back up the top.
>> Right.
>> So, if you have it on your wall, you do
that and then it would drop all the way
down and then you have to score again.
>> Okay.
>> Okay. So, you
>> Okay. So, you do that.
>> Oh.
>> And then Yeah, you got to score and it
keeps going down. How How
>> Oh, wow.
>> Wait, you broke it? You finished it?
>> No, it's going up. I just wanted to see
how how low does it how low didn't you
go? That's as low as it goes.
>> Yeah. So now now you just leave it cuz
you missed
>> and then [music] eventually it should
just come up.
>> That is coming up just really slowly. I
mean I think this is sick to be honest
for a kid. Yeah,
>> cuz they build it along with him.
>> Yeah, that's I mean he getting on it own
pointless but this is this is actually
the key part to think about.
>> Well, no. So the ones that you get
pre-built, he shows you how to code
them.
>> Oh,
>> so you can change it. So like you could
change the time of this and
>> I watched a Mark Forever video
yesterday. That's actually good for
kids.
>> That's sick. It's really really good.
>> It's something positive at least.
>> If you want your kid to be smart, just
get this.
>> How much are you paying? It's a monthly
subscription service.
>> Oh wow.
>> 20 doll hairs.
>> $20.
>> No, you get a box every month.
>> 50 $15 a month.
>> Okay. I was going to go with $30 maybe.
>> $24.99.
>> $30
>> cuz you're getting you're getting a
whole thing every
>> I guess. I guess it's
>> like getting like a puzzle every week.
Every month, sorry.
>> I don't know. For me, I thought this was
like nuts as in [music] sick.
>> I saw it on Netflix cuz you got Crunch
Labs on Netflix now.
>> He does. What do you guys put in this on
the tier list?
>> It has a positive thing for kids. So, we
gave Rods a B.
>> Give it an A.
>> I would back an A.
>> Okay. I'm happy with an A.
>> Yeah.
>> You sure you put No, no. I reacted to
the video yesterday. I was like, gassing
up. I was like, I'd personally put it in
like an S, but I'm happy with that.
>> S is reserved until I know everything
that's here. Fair enough. Fair. Okay.
David Dori. Wavers. Wavers. Back.
Waivers. Yeah. So, we have extra cheesy
hot honey pizza spicy pickle. So, do is
his pizza brand, right? Like he's got
>> [\h__\h]
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. I didn't even know he made these.
>> I'm surprised he didn't reach for that
extra cheesy. You want that cheesy? I
>> I'm going to try all of them.
>> Oh, they do look like they are like
quavers. Oh, they're w Oh, it makes
sense. SW quavers.
To be fair though, it is America and you
know that like potato chips in America
are crazy. That lace.
>> Oh my god.
>> Oh, bro. We may have uh
>> this might be Sier.
>> As long as the price isn't crazy crazy
soft melt in your mouth pizza.
>> Oh, is that one not good? Pizza one's
good.
>> I just don't know. M. It's not bad, but
I don't want it.
>> Oh, this is really good.
>> Oh, hot honey. Little spicy. That's a
hot part.
>> And then this is spicy. I hate pickles.
>> Same. It's not It's not awful, but it's
not good.
>> No, it's dead. Is it? Mm.
>> Damn. They are extra cheesy. I know
that's what they call, but they are.
[laughter]
>> [\h__\h] This might be S.
>> This might be S, too. You know,
>> I would eat all of this without
realizing.
>> How much would you pay for a bag,
though?
>> How much should a normal person pay for
a bag? [laughter]
>> American. You're going to go a bag. I'd
say 250.
>> How much a bag of Cheetos?
>> $250.
>> $250. I was going to go get $3.
>> A bag of Cheetos must cost like $34.
>> They only come in six pack.
>> Six pack. So I'm thinking like Yeah, but
I'm thinking like 15.
>> [\h__\h] $5 each.
>> $5 each.
>> Oh, might knock it down.
>> But that's that's that's all about
economies of scout. Think about this,
guys. It's a
>> But I can only buy six packs.
>> That's cuz of economies of scale. Once
they scale the business more, they can
make them cheaper. But for now,
>> we're saying it's $3 each, right? So it
should be 18. And if we have to buy six,
economies of scale, we should have to
buy 15. We should get $15. $30 is
higher.
>> They've not got enough quantity in total
yet. So, as a product is a B.
>> Oh,
>> because the price point is too high.
>> Fair. I mean,
>> for six of them.
>> It can't be S cuz of that.
>> B.
>> I'm going give it a
>> B+. Price point is my only argument
basically.
>> Damn.
>> If I could buy cuz also they come in
packs of six. I don't want the spicy
pick ones.
>> Yeah, true. I'm forced to have
>> you choose the flavors you get.
>> That's pretty good.
>> Well, you can choose it.
>> Hey, hey,
>> that might actually help it. So, do you
think the warehouse is full of of pickle
ones?
>> 100%.
>> Order some freaks of these still going,
by the way. So, maybe I
>> Yeah, let's take these away, please.
These are very good.
>> Oh, we have a web shooter by J Laser.
You always dreamed of being Well, this
looks What the hell?
>> Oh my god.
>> I thought it was going to look kind of
cooler than this, if I'm honest. You
want to try it?
>> Yeah. that go on then. Okay.
>> How do you spring load it?
>> This.
>> Oh yeah. Gone.
>> That was pretty effective to be honest.
>> Really push that in.
>> Yes. You got to get some momentum and
thrust. Okay. Your target is that
>> web shooter by J Laser.
>> Oh, now reel it back in.
>> It is kind of cool, but I feel like this
is going to cost like $30.
>> Also, are we going to get some kids
swinging in the street?
>> What? What do you mean by that?
No, let's say I'm a kid. I'm like, "Oh
my god, look. I I can now be
Spider-Man."
>> That was actually That was really cool.
>> But that sold me, by the way. That
actually did.
>> Yeah, but [laughter] it didn't stick to
anything.
>> Yeah, because you That's a web shooter,
not a web. It sticks to all.
>> Okay, wait. Let me
>> lick it as well.
>> All right.
>> Doesn't [\h__\h] stick to
>> Well, I mean,
>> how much is this, though?
>> It's got to be $20, man.
>> I think it's be more. I just I tried to
get the cop
>> that's like 40 bucks minimum.
>> Yeah,
>> see for me.
>> But obviously like you can get
Spider-Man ones that cost nothing.
>> I don't know. For me it's just not a
>> What a strange product. Do they?
>> No.
>> Why would you choose to go into this?
>> You're just It's like a [\h__\h] yo-yo.
>> Yeah, I'm already bored of it.
[laughter]
>> You You're also 32 years old. Quite the
demographic for it.
>> C. Yeah, I think I can back you on a C.
Packaging makes it a C.
>> I'm going to give it a D.
>> There is no D fail after C. And it
didn't fail though. It succeeded, right?
>> I mean, yeah, fine. Let's see.
>> We have Cheeky from Moist Critical.
>> Moist Critical.
>> Soap bags, soap tray.
>> Lots of soap in the search for
perfection. We succeeded.
>> It's all soap. Loi lavender moisturizing
body soap.
>> Okay. It's all about how it smells
though.
>> Absolute cinnamon. I like cinnamon. So,
>> this one's called touch grass.
>> Really?
>> Yeah. [laughter]
>> Touch grass soap.
>> Uh, this is pulp Francis.
>> So, this is designed to not dry out your
skin.
>> It's packed with shea butter and jaba
oil.
>> Smells so good.
>> They actually smell really good. Ah. Do
you like cinnamon?
>> No, not really.
>> Do you not?
>> This smells so good.
>> You do like cinnamon. I LIKE CINNAMON.
OH,
>> this one's quite nice.
>> Spoke. Spa soap.
>> No. And you get a
>> spa soap.
>> A soap tray.
>> Oh, it's so nice.
>> And you get a soap tray.
>> I actually love the fact he's made soap.
>> Yeah, it's so rare.
>> That's a proper mature That's a proper
mature man's product.
>> Please. When was the last time you used
soap?
>> I haven't. I hate using bars of soap.
Bars of soap are jarring. Maybe they can
make a cheeky shower gel range. Cheeky.
Why is it called cheeky? Cuz it's a
little cheeky bar of soap.
>> Shower gels would be better. Yeah,
>> cuz I Yeah, I don't remember the last
time I used soap. It's been a very long
time.
>> No, obviously I washed my hands
>> gel.
Test out the tray.
>> Six bars of soap plus the bag and the
tray.
>> I mean, it's a lot of soap and this is
this is lasting years.
>> That's true. I reckon it's going to be
like
>> thing is you only buy it once and then
you're sorted for like 10 years.
>> 60 bucks.
>> 60 BUCKS.
>> 60 BUCKS. You just said it's a lifetime
supply of soap. No, it's not. He just
said it once. Natural ingredients made
USA.
>> 35 bucks.
>> I think it should be 20. 20. $20.
>> You got six bars. So, tray 30s except
it's a gift set. So, like 34.
>> $20 should BE AN A.
>> 61. [screaming]
>> YOU KNEW IT. You must have known.
>> I didn't.
>> I've just done a lot of like guess the
price videos. I've got
>> You got a good repertoire of it. Now,
I'm I'm a fan of this branding, a fan of
the product,
>> but not the price.
>> But not the price as much. But I
understand pricing. Pricing isn't always
chosen by him.
>> So, what we saying?
>> I think a B is fair.
>> I think B.
>> Also, I'm not using these.
>> It's true. But is that a fail? No, but
for soap, everything it wants to be
qualifies for.
>> It's true. We'll go big.
>> It does the job. Yeah,
>> we'll go big.
>> What is this?
>> So, this
>> Oh my god. Is this a onesie?
>> This is from Loi Girl.
>> Oh, it's in the the girl on the train.
>> Yeah, that's Loi.
>> Look, you know the Lowi beats
>> live stream all day long and she sits
[\h__\h] on a train.
>> Wait, she's a real person.
>> Oh my god, I want those.
>> So, there slippers.
>> You want them?
>> Yes.
>> There you go. This is a This makes the
day better.
>> It's a jumper.
>> I don't want that.
>> No,
>> I thought it was a onesie.
>> And we also have
>> It is a onesie type thing.
>> No, it's a jumper. It's a What's it
called?
>> They're calling.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Noody, mate.
>> You got your slippers on. Oh,
>> they're unreal.
>> I feel like you have to be naked.
>> What?
>> Comfy though.
>> You listen to the lowfi and you want to
be cozy.
>> Yeah. Now I'm more chill than I could
ever been.
>> The issue is purely price point.
>> $100 in it.
>> If this is over $100, this is enough.
>> So, wait. Did you do you get the box
with two things and slippers?
>> Yeah. What are we judging here?
>> They're all individual.
>> Okay. I reckon both of these
>> Oh, so the slippers is final thing.
Yeah.
>> I reckon both of these are going to be
like $80.
>> No, this should be 50.
>> I think these are going to be
>> $50. Yeah. Or $50.
>> $40 cuz £50 is $70.
>> I reckon $40 and $80.
>> Yeah. How much are the slippers?
>> They're all the same price.
>> Oh,
>> $60. All of them.
>> Wait, wait, shut up. The shoes
>> these are sick.
>> Are the same price as this?
>> $70. $60.
>> Oh,
>> £60.
>> £50.
>> £45.
>> That's all right.
>> You know what?
>> That's actually okay.
>> I think that's that's a ripoff.
>> 47 Kid slippers is kind of crazy.
>> That's That's insane. This is fair.
[music]
>> This makes sense.
>> Although, I'm telling you, these are
unreal.
>> Well, you can have them.
>> I am. [laughter]
>> You've stolen them.
>> Um,
>> can I try home? because of the price of
those beh
>> I think bac
>> we have a dude perfect football
>> that's a hard thing to do well and dude
perfect jalapeno bacon Pinto beans.
>> Okay.
>> They don't come as a pair.
>> Surprised.
>> What a weird thing to do.
>> Pinto beans. How do you test pinto
beans? Cuz I need to be in like a polo.
>> He's got them. Oh, okay. Are these like
warmed up?
>> Oh, okay. Do we have any more
>> spuns?
[\h__\h] not on the pinto beans. Was it
jalapeno and bacon?
>> Pinto. Cheers, mate.
>> Cheers.
I quite like them. Bloody hell. Still it
still makes loud noise mouth. Doesn't
he?
>> You don't like them, do you?
>> No.
>> Cuz he does.
>> Me either.
>> Cuz you I know you like them.
>> It was I'll do it again then. Can you
Yeah. You have to try some for me.
>> Mm- It has actual bacon in it. So I
actually really like them. [laughter]
>> I Well, I'm giving it a C.
>> A C.
>> If you don't like them, why is it not a
fail? Because I'm trying to be nice.
>> But are we both the bull and the bean?
>> I think separately. How much are the
beans?
>> $4. It's in a tin actually.
>> Probably less than 10.
>> 22 250.
>> This was made by company, so I think
it's going to be cheap.
>> $5 for the tin.
>> Yeah, fair.
>> It's very nice.
>> I think they're quite nice.
>> I'm not a fan. Sorry.
>> And the ball?
$20. Now a ball is
>> test.
>> That's pretty good.
>> It actually feels like a good ball.
>> You're an expert. Can you do some cubby
or something? Or like bounce on your
head? did the head thing.
>> Wa!
>> It's passed the seal test now. Clap.
[laughter]
>> So, he's happy with the ball.
>> It's a decent ball.
>> Is that an A?
>> $20. I'd give that an A, you know?
>> Yeah. I'd give this an A and this a C.
>> I'm happy with it. I like that. But I
hear it. $5. Am I going to buy that $5
now?
>> No.
>> A C.
>> This is Hacksmith Saber. Now, I've got
to be careful here. Why?
>> Cuz it actually is actually like ping
out.
>> Wait, is it actually real? Wait, it's
real.
>> I don't know how to turn it on.
>> I'm kind of I'm kind of terrified.
>> I need to turn the lock off.
>> Does it come out the top? Yeah, not the
bottom.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Cool.
>> Imagine.
>> What? Oh, [\h__\h]
>> Lightsaber.
>> Wait, is that actually fire?
>> I am Darth.
>> Don't. No, don't. But you need to stop.
Is it real fire? I want to test it.
>> Yeah, we should test it. Okay. But what
are you going to do with that
afterwards? He's going to just He's just
going to drop it.
>> It's this.
>> But yeah, just
>> if it beans, it's fine.
>> You ready?
>> Whoa.
>> It is indeed real fire. It's real fire.
It
>> is real fire. I think this is really
cool.
>> This is sick.
>> Is that So that is that like a
>> You just press that.
>> Okay.
>> Hold it. Whoa. [screaming]
>> It is cool. Is it? I
>> think it's stabbing someone with this.
>> Well, lightsabers don't make much sense
anyway. It's a mini saber to be fair as
well. Oh, so it's like a little dagger
thing.
>> Yeah,
>> daggering.
>> You've seen you've seen a Star Wars,
right?
>> Yeah.
>> You always destroy stuff in it.
>> I tell you what, right, if you want to
give you want to get someone a Christmas
gift,
>> Ethan would love this. His his house
doesn't survive very long, but he would
love this. So, Faith, if you're
watching, this is a good gift. It
>> is quite cool.
>> Can you give me off? Get off it. Get off
it. All right. [snorts]
>> How much would you pay for that, though?
>> Uh, I'd pay £50.
>> Yeah. An expensive lighter would cost
you like 30 40 quid, wouldn't it? So,
>> I say I'd pay 50 quid.
>> 50 quid.
>> £75. It's not
>> It's not bad.
>> I'll give it an A. I thought it was
cool.
>> £75.
>> Uh, it's a bit pricey. That's why it's
not an S.
>> Okay.
>> Yeah.
>> A Yeah. A It does everything perfectly.
>> Jeremy fragrance. We have date for men
and office for men.
>> I'm going to open them, shuffle them,
and you have to. You don't know what
they smell like
>> exactly. But they're made
>> guess date and office.
>> They're made for two different things
scenarios. So you have to
>> I like it. If I can tell the difference.
>> It's a good product. That's what I'm
saying.
>> Why do I not do the back
>> and then do this hand? You can just
smell my hand if you want.
>> I can't smell anything really. I can
smell
>> I can definitely smell it.
>> I can smell it, but I can't tell what it
smells like.
>> It's quite nice. It's quite nice.
>> Can't even smell that one.
>> No. Wo. Oh,
>> I can smell that there's no one.
>> No, not really. First one's date.
>> I'd say no. I'd say this is office.
>> You think the first one is office?
>> First date. If you're trying to get
spicy. Yeah.
>> No, I'm going first date. Why do you
think this one is date?
>> Well, it just it's a bit stronger. You
want it to last longer because after the
date you, you know, go out clubbing.
>> I think you got your whole priorities
wrong here.
>> Have a good time and then, you know,
hopefully get a bit lucky.
>> You said that this one smells [music]
like it lasts longer. You spend more
time at the office than you do on a
date. A date is a few hours. offices.
You've been logged. That was a date.
That was the office.
>> Boom. Now I give it also sweeter, too.
It has like a little
>> Yeah.
>> Jeremy fragrance. Date for men. Office
smell.
>> I actually like the smell bottles.
>> I'd give it a
>> Well, how much?
>> There's a UK website price and there's a
US.
>> Okay. How much is it in America?
>> $99.
>> 99
>> for one.
>> What?
>> $100 for one. And in England?
>> Hi. 500
>> fail. No, that 500.
>> Thank you for getting it from America,
by the way.
>> What the [\h__\h] That's an F.
>> No, no, it's American product.
>> Jeremy famously has upped the price
continuously annoying all the time.
>> I'm giving it an F. Why? Cuz it's £500.
>> It's $99.
>> All right, let's All right, Josh, look
at this. Right,
>> cuz Dorough Bricks would be quid. We're
in England. This is in England for £500.
[music] But tell you this, right? Oh.
Oh, Simon. Oh, what what you wearing?
Oh, Josh, I spent £500 to wear office
for men.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. No. Cringe.
>> You're going to lose that.
>> I just No. No. Cringe.
>> 500 to wear office.
>> But I think we should rank him on a
basis of being American because Dori
bricks was in was in dots and
>> number in England, bro.
>> He doesn't have an English site.
>> It would cost 15 quid in UK.
>> That is mental. No, he's actually pissed
me off with that. That's a big f
>> £500.
So I'm thinking
>> Joy Right.
>> Joy Right. I've had I think these
before. Same.
>> So this is Ryan Treyan.
>> Sour.
>> Yeah, I've never I've seen these.
>> That's what I've had. I've had those.
>> I'm going to have a lot.
>> Sour rainbow ropes. That sounds delight.
Yeah. He's only number one candy in
Walmart. Is that what you find every
time? How much are these while we eat?
>> $8.99 for each for everything
>> each.
>> Oh, that's quite a lot.
>> That is a lot. Oh, I ain't spent $8.99
for any suite.
>> No.
>> What the [\h__\h]
>> Uh-oh. Someone scan the QR code on the
bag. This is a top secret video. I just
want you to know that this is You can't
really share this information with
anyone else.
>> It is delicious. What I found when I
tried these before is they're all like
stuck together.
>> Yeah.
>> And like really like
>> really sticky.
>> Yeah.
>> This normally is all like congealed and
stuck.
>> That's like when you get a pack of ham,
>> they're all stuck.
>> Oh, don't eat that anymore.
>> [laughter]
>> play mate. I don't know.
>> I like I like these when I had them
before.
>> They're not bad, but I'm not
>> I'm not going out my way to get out.
>> I'm not going out my way.
>> They are £8 as well. It's
>> too expensive.
>> In England, they have less sugar than
normal sweets. That's the whole point of
them.
>> Joy ride. Take the sugar away. More like
joy riders cuz they got rid of the joy
of sugar.
>> [\h__\h] that.
>> Cuz it tastes good. These are all right.
>> They [snorts] They do taste [laughter]
nice.
>> If we're going with English prices,
which we did for the last one, so I feel
bad. I've got to see. If it's in
America, I might go to like a B slash A.
>> I know. I just want my my sweets to have
sugar in it. That's the sole reason why
I get sweets.
>> As a parent, you still agree.
>> Yeah, she ain't got teeth. What's going
to fall out? [laughter]
>> A tongue.
>> Your tongue don't fall out if you eat
too much sugar
>> like right away. You never know. You
never know. You never know.
>> I'm saying C. I'm going to give it a B.
>> I'll give it a B.
>> Okay. So, we're at a B.
>> S. S.
>> F. We have W, which we know is Jake
Paul. Should be above S. M. W. Spray on
neck, chest, underarms in the shape of a
W. Wait. So, you go.
>> I don't think I'm going to spray myself.
>> You know,
>> I know. Is it Is it good?
>> Smells all right. You know, it smells
okay. Spray on neck, chest, and
underarms in shape of a W.
>> Noble. Am I stupid?
>> I don't think I'm high.
>> What the [\h__\h] is that?
>> No, no, no. You're not meant to smell it
that close. That's what
>> Holy [\h__\h]
>> No, you're not meant to smell it that
close.
>> [\h__\h]
>> We might be high. THAT WAS THAT WAS
>> [\h__\h] OH MY [\h__\h] HEAD.
>> Give me lightsaber.
>> [\h__\h] this guy, man. This guy s you need
to spray.
>> WAIT, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> NO, BRO. This is mental.
Actually, [laughter]
that was actually kind of cool.
>> Woohoo.
>> He's going to he's going to come back
into the thing, though.
>> Yeah, let's leave it there.
>> I'll do this properly. [\h__\h] sake.
>> W. Come on, put W. Yeah,
>> he's going to use that as an ad
>> for sure.
>> [\h__\h] [laughter]
>> We'll censor it. We'll cover Can we
change the W bottle in his hand?
>> Oh, it doesn't smell good.
>> It doesn't smell great. I'll be honest.
>> Uh, the blue one's all right. Let me
>> Well, don't use it. Of course. What's
happening here? Oh,
>> it it feels like it fits in an era of
like Lynx Africa, like OG Lynx when
you're first learning how to smell like
a decent human.
>> At least they smell good. Especially the
chocolate one.
>> This I think it smells all right.
>> No, man.
>> So, shampoo, conditioner, deodorant, and
a body wash. $40 for three things.
>> I'm actually pissed, man. I smell like
Jake Paul.
>> You smell like someone who's going to
win a fight against AJ. That's sick,
bro.
>> Um, yeah. Honestly, AJ might get knocked
out from this smell alone.
>> Directions. Are you reading this cuz you
don't know how to use shampoo? We might
have bigger problems, my friend. That's
pretty funny.
>> Yeah, but you haven't given me
directions.
>> Well, why is he being a [\h__\h] I just
bought his product
>> and I'm asking how to do it and you're
just saying you're laughing at me. I'm
going I'm going I'm going C tier. It
says nice hair fan on the back. Does it
scrub dubdub? Are you fily animals?
>> I'm sorry. If you buy this, you [music]
should get bullied.
>> Y'all smell nice. I'm going C. I can't
say fail because it is literally
>> That's an A for me by the way.
>> Shut up.
>> Are [laughter] you okay?
>> Is that an A? $40 for three things.
>> What are you giving it?
>> $40. Wait for this.
>> I didn't even clock that.
>> Those two plus the body wash $40.
>> Oh, so four things. Okay, I'm I'm
actually
>> I'm actually going to go B.
>> No, actually I hate this stuff.
>> Roll on.
>> Roll on is similar to Old Spice.
>> I think you meant to take off take off
the cover. How?
>> You got to just pull it off.
>> It's It's It's not
>> No, no, no, no. He We got to wait for
him to do it, bro.
>> Okay.
Lovely. [laughter]
>> He says, "Why have you [laughter]
>> Let me smell it. Let me smell it.
[music] Let me smell it, bro. Stop
trying to pull it on me. Oh my god, it's
got a trophy on it. It's so cringe."
>> No, she took it, bro. That's sick.
I'll happily give it a B, but I can't
go.
>> I'm giving that a C, man. Like, I can't
give it an F cuz it I guess technically
what it say.
>> Well, we think awful.
>> Easy B. Could be an A. [music] Okay.
It's okay. It's going B. I
>> Are you ever going to put that on your
armpit?
>> No, cuz I I USE BETTER ONES.
>> OH [\h__\h] OKAY.
>> This is targeted more towards like a
younger audience.
>> Our last product. All right. This is
from Vsauce.
>> Okay. Oh, I love it.
>> It has two It is leaking, but it has two
liquids in it. So, if you So,
>> you have Coke and water.
>> That's water.
>> Okay.
>> And then I believe you maybe twist it.
Wait,
>> maybe take the thing off. Take
>> Yeah, I want to get that off. Okay.
>> So, there's different holes. Okay. So,
>> Oh, that's cool.
>> How do I Wait, how does that work?
>> Well, there's absolutely no point in
that.
Oh,
>> there holes there, bro.
>> Why are there holes there?
>> There's legit holes. Look.
>> Nah.
Hang on. I love you. That's one of the
biggest. No. Okay. No. No. No. No. No.
No. No. I mean, I don't hate the concept
behind it, but it's not idiot proof.
Proven by us.
>> It's also very pointless.
>> You had something better.
>> Well, I have been to the cinema before
and had like the half and half things,
the slushies. Yeah.
>> And it has the thing in the middle. It's
like that. And you get two slushy
flavors in one.
>> Yeah. It's nice once every now and then.
>> The fact that we can't figure out within
two seconds
>> means it's a fail.
>> For me, it's a fail. I I don't know.
Josh in.
>> No, it's for sure. I'm just
>> Okay, if Josh can't figure it out. I'm
sorry.
>> Unless you like What you do is you get
two cups, right?
>> And you put them close
>> perfectly up next to each other.
>> You go this.
>> WA.
THERE we go.
>> Is that actually how it's supposed to
work?
>> No. No. Absolutely not. I'm so sorry.
It's an F. I mean, look at this. Look
what you've got. You have Zurka. Brainy
Zurker doing this.
What the hell is that?
>> So, there it is. That's our tier list
done. Thank you guys for watching.
>> Wait, there's one more.
>> What is it? We have a hat.
>> Oh,
>> it's a DanTDM hat.
[laughter]
>> Okay.
>> No, no, you are.
>> This is perfect. By the way, wear DanTDM
hat and hang on.
>> I'm going to wear it. Me and him, my
boys.
>> Okay.
>> You and your boys are about to be your
friends.
>> No, stop. Don't spray that on him.
>> No, no, no. Not that one, bro. I
[laughter] want to stop.
>> That's fire, bro.
>> Fire.
>> Oh my god. NOW, THANK [laughter] YOU FOR
WATCHING. GOODBYE, EVERYONE.
>> I love you, Dan. DDM.
>> Love you, Tan. DDM.